Guide to the Thain White Papers 1877-1983
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula,
- Photographs, 1877-1976; Series VIII; 2.75 linear feet; 758 photographs
  - European, 1914-1978; Subseries 5; 0.2 linear feet; 47 photos
    - Thiacourt Regnieville, France, 1918; 137(VIII):601
    - Thaicourt Regnieville, France, 1978; 137(VIII):602
    - Ypres, Belgium, Cloth Hall, 1915; 137(VIII):603
    - Ypres, Belgium, Cloth Hall, 1978; 137(VIII):604
    - Ypres, Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):605
    - Belgium, 1978; 137(VIII):606
  - Going-to-the-Sun Highway, circa 1931; Subseries 6; 0.1 linear feet; 17 photos
    This subseries contains photos of various scenes at Glacier National Park in Montana.
    - Homer Halverson with tractor, circa 1931; 137(VIII):607
    - Oil rig on lake, circa 1931; 137(VIII):608
    - Group of unidentified men standing by two old cars, circa 1931; 137(VIII):609
    - Oil rig on lake, circa 1931; 137(VIII):610
    - Jim Roland standing on some type of forestry equipment, circa 1931; 137(VIII):611
    - Miners at excavating site, circa 1931; 137(VIII):612
    - Near Upper St. Mary's Lake Narrows, circa 1931; 137(VIII):613
    - Near Upper St. Mary's Lake Narrows, circa 1931; 137(VIII):614
    - Men at ranger station, circa 1931; 137(VIII):615
    - A boat in dock at an unidentified lake, circa 1931; 137(VIII):616
    - Oil rig near shore of unidentified lake, circa 1931; 137(VIII):617
    - Oil rig near shore of unidentified lake, circa 1931; 137(VIII):618
    - Forest Rangers digging, circa 1931; 137(VIII):619
    - One mile west of Narrows of Upper St. Mary's Lake in Glacier Park, circa 1931; 137(VIII):620
    - Two men piling logs, circa 1931; 137(VIII):621
    - Encampment, circa 1931; 137(VIII):622
    - Piegan or half way between Sun Camp South Logan Pass, circa 1931; 137(VIII):623